(Penny:)Oh, my God. What is with you guys?
Well, it's not our fault.
Our dads never did anything like this with us.
- What, never?
- My dad was an anthropologist.
(Leonard:)The only father-son time he spent...
(Leonard:)...was with a 2000-year-old skeleton
of an Etruscan boy.
(Leonard:)I hated that kid.
(Raj:)Mine just took me to his gynecology office.
(Raj:)I got so bored, I'd put vaginal lubricant
at the bottom of my shoes...
...and pretend I was ice skating.
(Howard:)Yeah, well my quality father-son time
was spending my adolescence...
...Iooking out the window,
waiting for my dad to come back some day.
(Raj:)Yeah, okay, Howard wins.
(Leonard:)We didn't have opportunities like this
when we were growing up...
(Leonard:)...but right now there's a dad
that wants to take you on a fishing trip.
You're right. Ugh. I should do this.
Great. Ahem. Here you go.
Now what you do is, you stick your thumb
down its throat, grab the guts and pull.